本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
这就是我在重力泉最喜欢的地方了
This is it, dudes: my favourite place in Gravity Falls
我所有的知识都是从这里学来的
Everything I know I learned right here
这只青蛙告诉我怎么过马路
A frog told me how to cross a street
我在我的房子闹鬼的时候
When my house was haunted,
我学会了怎么吃掉鬼怪
I learned how to eat ghosts
这玩意还教了我怎么跳舞
And this thing taught me how to dance
我这一周都在跳快步舞
I've been jigging for 7 days straight!
苏斯
Soos?..
发生故障
让他自己享受吧
Let him have this
新游戏
请投币
恭喜你
Congratulations!
你赢了
You win!
请投币
小心点
Oh! Watch out!
哇  这是过场动画
Ooh, cutscene
空手道博士  你又把我父亲杀死了
Dr. Karate, you killed my father again!
你把这话给我收回去
You take that baaack!
开打
Fight!
耶耶耶  加油
Yeah yeah yeah! Go go!
赢家是朗博・麦克斯克尔米什
Our winner Rumble McSkirmish
胜利者永远都不会输
Winners don't lose!
怎么会这样  你肯定作弊了
What? You cheated
你最好把话给我收回去
You'll take that baaack!
第二局
Round 2
我要开始狠狠地打了
I'm gonna punch them rough
开打
Fight!
让他们赶快开始打起来
Let's gang up on them
你死定了
温蒂  怎么样啊  宝贝儿
Wendy! What's up babe?
我只是在为我的乐队贴传单
Just putting up some flyers for my band
我是吉他领队  没什么了不起的
I'm leading guitar. No biggie.
你涂了睫毛膏吗
Are you wearing mascara?
呃  这是男士用的
Um, it's eye-paint for men
罗比  迪普正在给我介绍这个超棒的游戏呢
Robbie, Dipper was just showing me this great game.
好啊  不错
Ah, yeah, sweet, sweet.
这一局你先旁观吧  冠军小孩
How's about you sit this one out, kid champ?
但我们才刚刚开始打这一局啊
But... We just started this round
嘿  放松点  哥们儿
Hey, relax, man
我是想跟我的女朋友
I'm just trying to spend
稍微玩一会儿  好吗
a ittle time with my girlfriend, all right?
我们只玩一局
It'll just be one round.
第三局  开打
Round 3. Fight!
明天我要跟我爸爸去野营  所以我一天都会不在
I'm going camping tomorrow with my dad, so I won't be around.
啊  不错  小心
Ah, cool, cool. Watch out!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： Howardxiao
校订： line  WaitinZ
■
后期： line  chocolate
怪诞小镇  第一季第十集
Gravity Falls  S01E10  Fight Fighters
一对王
King me!
这不公平
It's not fair!
她根本就不知道我们在玩什么
She doesn't even know what we're playing!
不是配对吗
Go fish?
哥们儿  我觉得我脑袋里可以收到电台
Dude. I think I'm picking up a radio station inside my head.
你眨一下眼  看看能不能换台
Try blinking to see if you can change the channel.
温蒂
We-endy-y!..
听起来是罗比在说话
Sounds like Robbie
罗比
Robbie?
是总是爱向温蒂
Is he that jerky twerp I
抛媚眼的那个混蛋吗
see making goo-goo eyes at Wendy all the time?
有一次他管我叫胖家伙  我的意思是
He called me big dude once. I mean,
虽然我的确是一个胖家伙  但是这话说出来挺伤人的
I am a big dude, but it kinda hurt.
你说我应该让摇摇继续向他呕吐吗
Should I sick Waddles on him again?
别冲动  虎猪
Easy, tiger!
我会摆平他的
I'll handle it.
哈哈  有好戏看了
Ha-ha, conflict
温蒂  温蒂温蒂  温蒂
Wendy, Wendy-Wendy, Wendy!
出来吧  赶快下来
Come on out, girl! Come on down!
你其实已经知道她不在这里了吧
You realize she's not here, right?
呸  是的
Pssh. Yes.
什么
What?
今天她全家都去野营了
She's out camping with her family today.
如果你真的认真听过她说话的话  你应该知道的
Maybe if you listened to her for once, you'd know that.
你说什么
What was that?
我只是说过她不在
I just said she's not here.
不不不  你想搅这趟浑水吗
No-no-no. You wanna get into it, huh?
谁想搀和啊  小朋友
Who wants get into it, kid?
你还以为我不知道发生了什么  是吧
You think I don't know what's been going on, huh?
显然你很喜欢我的女朋友
It's obvious, you've gotta thing for my girlfriend,
难道不是吗  不是吗
Don't you? Don't you?
什么  绝对没有  拜托
What? No! Come on, man!
是啊  我很确定她现在非常渴望跟一个
Yeah. I'm sure she's just dying to ask out 12 year old kid
每天都穿同一条短裤的十二岁小孩约会
who wears the exact same shorts every day
嘿  我有一个主意
Hey, here's an idea.
要不我现在就给她打电话
Why don't I call her right now
让我们看看她是不是真的想跟你约会
and see if she wants to go out on a date with you.
嘿  不要  你完全没必要做这个
Hey! Look! Don't... You don't have to!
不要  拜托了
Don't, please, man!..
你要做什么  哼
What are you gonna do, huh?
什么  什么
What? What?
我的手机
My phone!
我会赔你一个新的
I'll buy you a new one
不  你就是跳进黄河也洗不清你的罪名了
Oh no. You're not getting off that easy!
嘿  你们在这儿打架被我抓到了吧
Hey, I know a fight when I see one.
给我待在这儿别动
Stay right there!
我和你  三点钟  在公园  不见不散
You, me, Circle Park, 3 o'clock.
我们要做个了断
We finish this!
哎  他走了
Oh, he's gone.
我本想找几个朋友下赌注呢
I was just gonna call the boys over to place a few bets
我们打赌穿紧身牛仔裤的打架会赢
The smart money's on skinny jeans.
当时我到底是怎么想的啊  我根本就不能打架
What was I thinking? I can't fight!
我也从来没有打过架
I've never been in a fight before
我的胳膊细得跟麻杆似的
Look at these noodle arms!
直接猛击他的头嘛
Just bonk him over the head.
这是一个天然的静音键
It's nature's snooze button.
先生们
Boys!
你们怎么就不会将不满藏在心中呢
Why can't you learn to hate each other in secret?
像我们女孩子那样
Like girls do.
好啊  就听你妹妹的
Sure, listen to your sister
说不定还可以分享你们的衣物呢
Maybe you can share dresses too.
哈哈哈  砰
Ha-ha-ha Boom!
可能他会忘掉这件事吧
Maybe he'll just forget about it?
说不定会大事化小呢
Maybe it'll all blow over.
我不知道啊  青少年是个危险的群体
I don't know Dipper. Teenagers are dangerous.
那些荷尔蒙激素把他们变成了杀人机器
Those hormones turn them into killing machines.
真的吗
Really?
是啊哥们儿  我的堂兄雷吉
Oh yeah dude. My cousin Reggie got
就在青年时期被卷进了一场打架
in a fight with teen once.
那人全身被打得
The guy broke like...
手臂断了  腿也差不多了
All his arms... All his legs...
我觉得他杀了他或者怎么的  我也不是很清楚
I think he killed him or something, I don't know.
我和雷吉最近才说过这事呢
Me and Reggie were just talking about it.
我在这里呆不下去了  如果罗比找上门了怎么办
I can't stay here. What if Robbie comes back?
我要躲起来
I gotta hide!
听着  孩子  你现在就要做出选择
Look kid. You've got yourself a choice here.
你是像个男人一样勇敢去迎战呢
You could either go face him like a man.
还是像个懦夫一样躲在屋子里
or you can hide indoors, like a wimp.
你选什么
What will it be?
你选择了懦夫
Wimp it is.
拜托你了  苏斯  罗比比我足足高一倍
Come on, Soos. Robbie is twice my size!
我的意思是  人死了人生就没意义了
I mean, what would getting myself killed accomplish?
我只需要在这里藏过三点钟而已
I just need to hide here until 3 o'clock passes.
这个日子真是漫长
This day will never end.
放松点  迪普  就别去想罗比了
Relax, Dipper. Just try not to think about Robbie.
姑娘  你为什么要这么怪怪
Girl, why you ackin' so cray-cray?
“你为何如此怪怪”广告之后  马上回来
"Why you ackin' so cray-cray" Will be back in a moment
可怜的迪普
Poor Dipper.
躲着罗比  而无法直面恐惧
Hiding from Robbie, unable to face his fears.
傻瓜才会害怕  这就是我从不恐惧的原因
Fears are for chumps. That's why I don't have any.
要我帮你找一个梯子吗
You want me to go get a ladder?
- 我们根本就没有   - 什么
- We don't have one. - What?
调查显示  在屋子里面放梯子比
You know, study shows that keeping a ladder inside the house
一个上膛的手枪更危险
is more dangerous than a loaded gun
所以我有十支枪
That's why I own ten guns:
可以防止有疯子用梯子来潜入我们家
in case some maniac tries to sneak in a ladder.
拜托  你为什么要如此怪怪
Grunkle Stan! Why you ackin' so cray-cray?
你才是那个怪怪的人呢
You're the one who's ackin' cray-cray!
我要走人了
I gotta go now.
为什么斯坦叔公一谈到梯子就如此奇怪啊
Why would Grunkle Stan be so weirded out by ladders?
原来如此
Of course!
我猜他不想告诉我们他有恐高症
I think he has a secret fear of heights!
咱们要试试他
We'll have to test him to be sure.
当然也可以不管它啦
Or we could leave well enough alone.
才不会呢
Na-a-ah!
天哪  我想知道真正在游戏里面
Man. I wonder what it's gonna
的感觉会是怎么样的
be like to go inside a video game for real.
我在几年前就该想到这一招才对
I should have thought of this years ago!
傻蛋罗比  真是个混蛋
Stupid Robbie, such a jerk.
第四局  开打
Round 4. Fight!
KO
K.O.
你要继续吗
Continue?
一个真正的胜利者从不逃避战斗
A winner never runs away from a fight!
你说起来倒是容易
That's easy for you to say
你可是有很多条命的
You have more than one life!
真希望游戏中能出来一个人来帮我打败罗比
I wish one of these guys could fight Robbie for me.
释放终极能量
"To unleash ultimate power?"
我倒是挺喜欢终极的事情
I do like things that are ultimate.
后  后  停  前  后  前
Back, back, hold, forward, back, forward,
下  停  四分转  转一圈  三连击
down, hold, quarter, circle forward, triple punch!
貌似没有用啊
I guess it didn't work.
呃  苏斯
Uh... Soos?
请选择角色
Select your character!
朗博・麦克斯克尔米什
Uh... Rumble McSkirmish?
你是真实存在的吗
You're real?
击掌
High five!
哎  你的像素让我的手好痛啊
Ow! Your pixels are really sharp!
你好小朋友
Greetings child boy!
我是来自美国的朗博・麦克斯克尔米什
I'm Rumble McSkirmish from a USA!
打拳  踢腿  打拳  踢腿
Punch Kick Punch Kick!
哇  真帅
Ow! Cool!
变形器  把我变为一个超级猛狼
Change machine! Change me into a powerful wolf!
如果让罗布来比赛的话
With Rumble around Robbie
罗比会失去战意的  我都根本不需要动手
will be so scared I won't even need to fight him
我的保镖竟然是世界上最牛的战士
I've got the world's greatest fighter to be my bodyguard!
我要喝药了
I need power-ups!
这真是棒极了  我要给苏斯看看
This is so amazing! I've got to show Soos!
苏斯
Soos?
救我  我被困在游戏里面了
Help! I'm trapped in a game!
理论上来说挺酷的  但我发现实际上这真是太无聊了
It was cool in theory but in practice it was really boring.
这不仅仅只是一场游戏了
It's not just a game anymore.
好啦  摇摇  让我们开始进行
Alright Waddles. It's time to begin
让斯坦克服恐高症行动
Operation Get Stan Over His Fear Of Heights!
这名字是我起的
I came up with that name.
好叔公节快乐
Happy Great Uncle's Day!
有好叔公这个节日吗
There's a Great Uncle's Day?
肯定不是我瞎编的
Of course it's not a day I've made up
高跟鞋  你不应该有这个的
High heels! You shouldn't have
说真的  这到底是什么
Seriously. What... What is this?
有问题吗
What's wrong?
你是想说这些高跟鞋太高了吗
Are you saying these heels are too high?
它们会把你弄得不舒服
Do they make you uncomfortable?
- 可能吧  - 你就承认你有恐高症吧
-Maybe  -Admit it! Admit you have a fear of heights!
什么  这就是你送我这些的原因吗
What? That's why you bought me these?
你应该为你自己感到惭愧
You should be ashamed of youself!
尤其是今天还是好叔公节
And on Great Uncle's Day no less!
但不  我没有恐高症
But no, I don't have a fear of heights.
现在让我们观看世界上最吓人的跳伞节目
We now return to world's most terrifying skydiving!
啊  赶快关掉它
Ah! Ah! Ah! Turn if off!
貌似我真的有恐高症
So I have a fear of heights.
这真的很怪怪吗
Is that really so cray-cray?
我们这里没有传统的能量药剂
We don't have any traditional power-ups.
火鸡腿  披萨  和金圈圈
Turkey legs, pizza boxes or golden rings
你想吃这半个玉米卷吗
How about half a taco?
把它放在地板上
Place it on the floor.
装备：
获得新武器
半个玉米卷
真希望我也能这样
I wish I could do that!
现在我必须打败世界上最厉害的战士
Now I must defeat the world's greatest fight fighters!
现在带我去苏联
Take me to the Soviet Union!
由于很多原因  这件事情很难办到
That's gonna be tough. For a number of reasons.
不过我知道在怪诞小镇这里有一个战士
But I do know a fighter here in Gravity Falls.
满状态吗
Maximum power?
他的名字是罗比・V  他算是我的敌人吧
His name is Robbie V. And he's kinda my archenemy.
他杀了你爸爸吗
Did he kill your father?
倒没有  他是我的情敌
Well, he's dating the girl I like
而且他很喜欢在微博上刷屏  很烦人
and he posts a really annoying amount of status updates.
然后他就杀了你的父亲
And then he killed your father!
呃  是的
Uh, sure.
不管怎么样  我希望你能帮我吓吓他
Anyway, I was hoping you could scare him off for me,
这样我就不用跟他打架了
so I don't have to fight the guy?
你的问题使我肌肉大绷
Ha-ha-ha! Your question makes my shoulders bounce!
火球术  上钩拳  下勾拳  碗攻击
Fireball! Uppercut! Downercut! Bowl of punch!
你会帮我打败罗比吗
So you'll protect me from Robbie?
任务接受  请按开始键
Challenge accepted! Press Start!
糟糕  我叔公好像来了
Oh-oh. I think I hear my uncle
请站好不要动
Stay perfectly still.
我让你站着不动
I said stay still.
我只能不动到这个程度了
This is as still as I can stay
你说我该怎么让斯坦叔公克服恐高症呢
How I'm gonna get Grunkle Stan over his fear of heights?
梅宝  你跟朗博打过招呼了吗
Hey Mable. Have you met Rumble yet?
他是我的新保镖
He's my new bodyguard
这位小朋友给了我一个玉米卷
The child gave me a taco!
哇  他的声音真粗
Wow! He's got a crazy voice!
把这些单词念出来
Here, say these words
欢腾
Effervescent!
馅饼
Applefritter!
核黄素
Riboflavin!
梅宝  他不是一个玩具  他是我的打架机器
Mabel, he's not a toy, he's a fighting machine
我要让他帮我抵御罗比
I'm gonna get him to defend me from Robbie
不感觉这等于作弊吗
Isn't that kinda like cheating?
我猜是的
I guess so
不管怎么样  打完架再见你
Well, I'll see you after the fight.
狗屎  大狗屎
Poop! Poppenbuts!
把我对手的大招告诉我
Tell me my opponent's special moves.
别担心  他看到你的时候会吓得尿裤子的
Don't worry. As soon as he sees you, he's gonna wet his pants.
尿湿的裤子肯定比不过这玩意
His wet pants will be no match for this!
哇  这是哪来的
Woah! Where did that come from?
我打了一个油桶
I punched an oil drum!
相信我吧  你不会用上这个的  吓吓他就可以了
Trust me, you won't need that. Just give him a good scare.
好吧
Yes!
用这个
With this!
这条街怎么有这么多危险的垃圾
This street has really dangerous litter
嘿  斯坦叔公
Hey Grunkle Stan!
想试试蒙着眼睛
How would you like to go take a walk
出去随便散散步吗
nowhere in particular while wearing a blindfold?
呵  确实比坐着等死好
Huh! Beats just sitting around being old.
等一下
Wait a minute!
你不会是想把我带到
You're not planning on
什么超级高的地方吧
taking me somewhere super high up, are you?
斯坦叔公  我绝对不会的
Grunkle Stan! I would never!
我以童子军的名义起誓
Scout's honour!
好吧  咱们走吧
All right. Let's go.
好啊  看看谁过来了
Well-well-well, look who decided to show up.
我还以为你怕了呢
I thought you chickened out.
你准备好以男人的方式解决这件事了吗
You ready to settle this like men?
哥们儿  我不觉得你真的想跟我打
Look dude, I don't think you wanna fight me.
咱们在有人受伤之前和解吧
Let's just call this thing off before someone gets hurt.
你怕了  是吧
You're scared, huh? Is that it?
好吧  这是你自找的
Ok dude. You asked for it.
他是谁啊  他为什么看起来这么模糊
Who's your friend? And why is he blurry?
这是世界上最好的战士了
This happens to be the greatest warrior that ever lived.
好吧  嘿  独眼龙  这孩子答应给你什么了
Yeah, right. Hey eyepatch, what have the kid promised you
给你的前臂多加点皱纹
more tate for your forearms?
你都把他的父亲给杀了  你竟然还敢笑出来
How can you laugh when you killed this boy's father?!
等等  什么
Wait, what?
我给你最后一次机会  现在马上走人
I'm giving you one last chance: back down,
否则我就管不住这家伙了
or this guy is gonna go nuts.
还是你滚蛋吧  小屁孩
How about you back down, kid!
你自找的  朗博  上
You asked for it. Rumble, go!
什么
What the?..
什么  发生了什么事
Wha... What is happening?
我本来不想这样的  这是你逼我的
I didn't want to do this, man, but you gave me no choice.
现在你不想惹我了吧
Maybe now you won't mess with me.
朗博  你可以停了  我觉得他已经受够了
Woah! Rumble, you can stop! I think Robbie's had enough!
朗博上投
Rumble Throw!
停下来  给我停下来
Stop! I said stop!
什么  那家伙疯了
What the? That guy is crazy!
火球术
Fireball!
这大爷的是什么
What the heck was that?
我只让你吓吓他  你都快要把他打死了
You're only supposed to scare him, you almost killed him!
我绝对不会饶过侮辱你的人
I will not rest until the man who dishonoured you
除非他陨灭了
is DESTROYED!
拳击
Punch!
情况不妙
This isn't good
我有种感觉  他会先来这边
Something told me this would be his first stop
淡定
Chill out man!
求求你了  朗博  别打了
Please, Rumble, you gotta stop!
朗博  等等
Rumble, wait!
我打  我打  我打
Punch-punch-punch!
你不用这么做的
You don't have to do this.
至少你走慢点
At least pace yourself.
否则你会痉挛的
You might get a cramp.
老爸  我爱死你了
I love you dad!
奖励        关卡
满分     过关
哎  我的车
Oh! My car!
我们买辆新的就可以了
We'll just buy another one
我喜欢当富人
I love being rich
能打的都打光
All you can hit!
嘿  哥们儿
Hi dude!
苏斯  你跑到哪里去了
Soos! Where have you been?
说来话长了  伙计
Long story, man.
你看到了吗
Dude, did you see that
有个人从游戏里面出来了  他摧毁了他看到的一切东西
video game guy destroying everything in sight?
真是太疯狂了
That's crazy!
是啊  我貌似让他活过来了  然后让他做我的保镖了
Yeah, I kinda sorta brought him to life to be my bodyguard
不过现在我要在他把罗比杀掉之前阻止他
But now I have to stop him before he kills Robbie!
你需要一个开着皮卡的可爱助手吗
You need an amiable sidekick with a pickup truck?
你知道我要的
You know I do!
现在把你的蒙眼罩拿下来
Take off your blindfold NOW!
是啊  和我想的差不多
Yeah, that's pretty much what I was expecting.
你比我想象的更坚强
You're doing better than I thought!
现在朝扶手栏杆外面看
Now look over the handrail.
不要
Nope.
你感觉到愤怒和荷尔蒙了吗
Hey, do you smell anger and hormones?
现在我安全了
Finally, I'm safe.
嘿  罗比  找你自己的水塔去
Hey, Robbie, get your own water tower!
小声点  他会发现我们的
Shh, keep it down, he'll find us!
找到对手了
Challenger sighted!
得拯救世界了  哥们儿
On to save the day, dude
你可以去躲  但是你躲不过我
You can hide, but you cannot hide!
朗博  你得停下来  听我说
Rumble, this has to stop, please, listen to me!
踢腿
Kick!
发生什么事了
What was that?
天哪
Oh boy.
我们应该还是安全的吧
We're safe, right?
当然不是  这塔在摇晃呢
Of course not! This thing is on stills!
我们在很高的地方
High, high up!
拳击
Punch!
干掉他
Finish him!
不要  不要把我杀掉
No no no! Don't! Don't finish me!
朗博
Rumble!
朗博  我要告诉你一些话
Rumble, I have something to tell you
罗比
Robbie...
罗比没有杀死我的父亲
Robbie didn't kill my father.
那是谁做的
Then who did?
什么
What?
我父亲还活着呢  我对你撒谎了
No one did, I lied to you
那你实际上是一个
Then you're actually a...
坏蛋
bad guy!
我觉得我还真是呢
I guess I kinda am...
我所做的一切
My entire journey
竟然是为了一个谎言  我的尊严被侮辱了
A lie. My honour has been insulted.
先生告诉我不要跟邪恶搅浑在一块儿
Sensei warned me not to join the path of evil
这小孩子竟然让我误入歧途
The boy has led me astray from my teachings
如果罗比・V不是最终挑战者
If Robbie V. Is not the last stage,
那就是
then it must be...
你
Yooouuuuuuuuuuu!
哥们儿
Dude!
千万别跟他打架
Don't fight him, man
这家伙简直就是黑带中的黑带
That guy's got like the black belt wrapped around his black belt
你会被杀死的
You could get killed.
我得去面对他
I have to.
这事是因我而起的  至少我要试着来平息它
I started all this, and I've got to at least try to stop it
你确定你不会像一个懦夫那样躲起来
You're sure you wouldn't rather hide like a wimp?
看来你要像男人一样去战斗啊
Fight like a man it is.
准备
Ready!
开打
Fight!
火球电球一起攻击
Fireball and lightning ball through
火球术
Fire!
哈哈  你打架的样子像个女生一样
Ha ha ha! You fight like a girl!
你本来就是一个小宝宝
Who was also a baby!
糟糕
Oh no.
倒也值得试试
That was worth a shot
糟糕  我没有能向上攻击的
No. I have no looking up
招数
...animation!
我该怎么办呢  把他卷起来然后挂在我墙上
What should I do? Roll him up and put him on my wall?
哥们儿  我们猜拳决定吧
Dude! We should rock paper scissors for him.
拳
Fist
击
punch
雨
rain!!!
别低估了我  我还有拳击能力呢
Never underestimate that I have punches!
超级
Super
能量
power
忍者
ninja
增强
turbo
全新
neo
极端
ultra
高级
hyper
超强
mega
多功能
multi
混沌
alpha
原初的
meta
更大能量
extra
之终极
uber
前置
prefix
连击
combo!!!
你的确是冠军中的冠军
You sir truly are the champion of champions
朗博赢了
Rumble wins!
一个真正的胜利者永远都不会输
Winners don't lose!
我还真不敢真正认同呢
I wouldn't be too sure about that, man
游戏结束
Game Over!
什么  不要
What? No! No!
不
Noooooooo!
老朋友  游戏结束了
Game over, old friend
多谢       玩家         参与
哈哈  不错  哥们儿
Ha-ha, nice one, dude
很抱歉  斯坦叔公
I'm sorry, Grunkle Stan.
我还以为这有用呢  不过我错了
I thought this would help but I was wrong.
错得厉害
So wrong!
我活下来了
I... I survived!
劫后余生的感觉真好
I survived and I feel great!
等等  让我跳个骄傲舞试试
Wait. Let me do a cocky dance just to be sure.
哈哈  来吧  世界
Ha-ha! Deal with it, world!
斯坦・派恩不再恐高了
Stan Pines is cured of his fear of heights!
-孩子  你下来不  -不
- You're coming kid?  - Uh-huh.
怎么啦  现在你恐高啦
What's the matter? You've got a fear of heights now?
糟糕
Oh-oh.
什么  那人是谁
What? Who was that guy?
为什么你在我身边的时候
Why is it that whenever you're around,
总有幽灵怪兽之类的东西出现
there's always ghosts and monsters and whatever?!
我不知道  伙计
I don't know, man.
那家伙快把我脖子拧断了  你知道我现在有多生气吗
That guy almost broke my neck. You know how mad I am right now?
所以我猜我们现在要开始打了  不是吗
So I guess you and I have to fight now, huh.
来吧  你爱打多痛就打多痛
Go ahead, man. Do your worst.
我只想把这事情解决掉
I just wanna get this over with.
那我现在要好好享受了
Oh man, I'm so gonna enjoy this.
-你不准备跑吗  -不会的
Aren't you gonna run? - Nope.
确定吗
Are you sure?
呸  打你又有什么用
Pfft. It's not ever worth it.
我是首席吉他手  我还得节省力气呢
Playing lead guitar, so I'm gonna save my hands.
嘿  两位  我听到了一些来自这里的狂吼呢
Hey guys, I heard some crazy screaming out here
-温蒂  -温蒂  你回来了
Wendy?! - Wendy?! You're back!
是啊  天  这里发生了什么啊
Yeah, man. Oh. What the heck happened here?
变态龙卷风这类的
Freak tornado or something?
呃  那个
Uhh... Well...
还有为什么你们都鼻青脸肿的
And why are your faces all jacked up?
你们不会在打架吧
You guys weren't fighting each other, were you?
我最讨厌男人打架了
I hate it when guys fight
-打架  没有  -不  我们从来没有打过
- No, fighting? - No, why would we? Never!
我们为了防止另外两个人打架
We actually fell down trying
还摔了几个跟头呢
to stop two other guys from fighting each other
真棒  看到你们两个相处如此和谐  我开心极了
Cool. Really makes me happy to see my two boys hanging out.
我得去放行李了
I've got some unpacking to do.
等会儿给你们发短信
I'll text you guys later.
听到了吗  她把我当作她的两个男人中的一个哦
Did you hear that? She called my one of her two boys!
她看的可是我啊
She was looking at me though
罗比  如果我们仍然这么
Look, Robbie. If we stay
憎恨对方的话  温蒂会抛弃我们两个的
at each other's throats, we'll both lose Wendy
咱们就打冷战吧
We need to make a cold war pact.
好啊  怎么办
Ok. What's that?
我们要学会在沉默中憎恨他人
We need to learn to just hate each other in silence.
你的意思是
You mean, like...
像女孩子做的那样
What girls do?
没错  像她们做的那样
Yeah, exactly. What girls do.
然后我跟汤普森说
So then I told Thompson:
嘿  给我们留点
"Hey! Save some for the rest of us!"
好故事  温蒂
Good one, Wendy!
天哪  等等
Oh, man. Just a second
就像我刚说的
So as I was saying
没错  我知道你是最棒的
Yeah, I know, you're the best!
我是迪普  我富有决策力  还有一条短裤
I'm Dipper. I have shorts and determination!
是我  梅宝
It's-a me, a-Mabel!
我虽然走路慢  但我跳的很高
I'm slower, but I jump higher!
选择我  要不就算了
Pick me or whatever.
好吃  好吃
Yum-yum-yum-nom-nom-yum-yum
哎呀  只是个梦而已
Alas, 'twas not but a dream.
把我朋友都吃了
Eating my friends